PAVLO STATKEVYCH

<u>Date of Birth:</u> 28/08/1989 <u>Place of Birth:</u> Ukraine <u>Nationality:</u> Ukrainian <u>Tell:</u> +380508337694

00/0046

E-mail: p.statkevich@gmail.com

Website/Portfolio: www.pavlostatkevych.com

PROFILE

As a self-educated developer I have reached a point where I understood that I needed to join a team of experienced developers to improve my skills and knowledge of web design technologies by participating in development of innovative solutions. Supervised by a couple of experienced developers I was using online resources like Treehouse, Code School and Pluralsight to learn about front-end web development. Experience in development of my own portfolio website (www.pavlostatkevych.com) and other attached to it websites (www.pavlostatkevych.com) pavlostatkevych.com and persistence helps me to finish what I start. My experience in sales and management will help me to organize myself, quickly join a project and figure out necessary business processes to implement a particular product. Man

EXPERIENCE

02/2016 - now	Personal portfolio website <u>www.pavlostatkevych.com</u> including 10+ attached projects.
02/2014 - 08/2015	Sales Manager for Coca-Cola Beverages Ukraine Limited – Kiev, Ukraine.
03/2013 - 02/2014	Head of Sales Department for SK "Express Trade" – Kiev, Ukraine.
03/2008 - 03/2013	From salesman to Deputy Executive Officer for "Unitrade Group", ltd – Kiev, Ukraine.

EDUCATION

10.2015 - now	Supervised by two experienced developers, studied front-end development from
	online resources: "Code School - <u>www.codeschool.com</u> ", "Team Tree House -
	www.teamtreehouse.com", "Pluralsight - www.pluralsight.com".
03/2013 - 08/2013	Finished SK "Express Trade" internal management training course.
08/2009 - 09/2009	Finished "Unitrade Group" internal "Master of Sales" course.
09/2004 - 07/2007	Studied at Tsyurupinsk Agricultural College.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3 (Responsive), JavaScript, JQuery

Networking: TCP/IP, FTP, HTTP, VPN

Tools: Sublime Text 2 + Emmet, Photoshop, MSOffice

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Languages: Ukrainian (native), Russian, English

Personal Good problem solving skills, disciplined, persistent, hardworking, initiative, adequately **qualities:** react to constructive criticism, able to work under pressure, responsible, honest, sociable.

Hobbies: Gym, video games, traveling, pool.